ethiopian.tv 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – Ethiopian News and Entertainment

Ethiopian.tv Privacy Policy

At ethiopian.tv, we never sell your personal information to third parties. We also recognize that the privacy of our visitors to ethiopian.tv and the security of their personal information is very important. Therfore, this privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by ethiopian.tv and how it is used and how we safeguard your information.

Log Files

As with most other websites, ethiopian.tv makes use of log files. The information in the log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you used to visit this site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons

This site, ethiopian.tv, uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences and record information about which pages are visited. This information is used to customize ethiopian.tv pages based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor’s web browser sends.

Ethiopian.tv uses third party advertisement partner such as the Google AdSense program. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on this site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit this site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing movie ads to someone who frequents movie sites).

DoubleClick DART Cookie

– Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to ethiopian.tv.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to ethiopian.tv and/or other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with this site as well as other websites.
